

1987 February 1

## Personal Profile

Web developer with troubleshooting skills and experience building web systems. Trained for teamwork under the agile SCRUM methodology. Selftaught and always willing to learn new development tools for my personal and professional growth.

## Contact



+34 663 48 34 44



chalds87@gmail.com



Galicia - Spain



chalds.github.io

# Soft Skills

- Leadership.
- Analytical Thinking.
- Teamwork.
- Perspective.
- Solve Problems.
- Patience and Perseverance.
- Focus and productivity.
- Proactive.

# **Christian Lopez**

Web Developer

# Work Experience

#### **Analyst Developer**

Infoguia.com 2016 - 2023

- Maintenance of the different existing systems in the company.
- Design and creation of new key internal systems for the operation of the company.
- Technical support to other team members.
- In charge of front end development of web applications using the VueJs Javascript framework for the consumption of APIs created with the PHP Laravel framework.

#### **Front End Developer**

#### Roomleader (Grupo Hotusa) 2023 - Present day

- Front end development of modules for the websites of the hotels belonging to the Hotusa Group.
- Front end development of newsletters
- Front end development with the React Js framework

### Tech Stack

- JavaScript.
- PHP.
- VueJs.
- Visual Studio Code.
- Trello Board.
- GitHub Desktop.
- Microsoft Teams.
- Discord.

### Idiomas

#### Spanish:

Native

#### **English**

Intermediate level



1987 February 1

## Personal Profile

Web developer with troubleshooting skills and experience building web systems. Trained for teamwork under the agile SCRUM methodology. Self-taught and always willing to learn new development tools for my personal and professional growth.

## Contact



+34 663 48 43 444



chalds87@gmail.com



Galicia - Spain



chalds.github.io

# Soft Skills

- Leadership.
- Analytical Thinking.
- Teamwork.
- Perspective.
- Solve Problems.
- Patience and Perseverance.
- Focus and productivity.
- Proactive.

# **Christian Lopez**

Web Developer

## Education

Colegio Universitario Francisco de Miranda Computer Engineer | 2012 - 2016

Platzi Online Course Basic Programming Course | 2017

Platzi Online Course Introduction to PHP | 2017

## Personal reference

**Daniel Gómez Matos** +34 722 63 76 00



1987 Febrero 1

### Perfil

Desarrollador web con habilidades para solucionar problemas y experiencia en creación de sistemas web. Capacitado para el trabajo en equipo bajo la metodología ágil SCRUM. Autodidacta y siempre dispuesto a aprender nuevas herramientas de desarrollo para mi crecimiento personal y profesional.

# Contacto



+34 663 48 34 44



chalds87@gmail.com



Galicia - España



chalds.github.io

## Habilidades Blandas

- Liderazgo.
- Pensamiento analítico.
- Trabajo en equipo.
- Perspectiva.
- Resolución de problemas.
- Paciencia y perseverancia.
- Enfoque y productividad.
- Proactivo.

# **Christian Lopez**

Desarrollador Web

# Experiencia laboral

## **Analista Programador**

Infoguia.com 2016 - 2023

- Mantenimiento de los diferentes sistemas existentes en la empresa.
- Diseño y creación de nuevos sistemas internos clave para el funcionamiento de la empresa.
- Apoyo técnico a otros miembros del equipo.
- Encargado del desarrollo Front End de aplicaciones web usando el framework de Javascript VueJs para el consumo de APIs creadas con el framework de PHP Laravel.

#### **Developer Front End**

#### Roomleader (Grupo Hotusa) 2023 - Actualidad

- Maquetación web de modulos para las webs de los hoteles pertenecientes al Grupo Hotusa.
- Maquetación de newsletters
- Desarrollo front end con el framework React Js

# Herramientas Técnicas

- JavaScript.
- PHP.
- VueJs.
- Visual Studio Code.
- Trello Board.
- GitHub Desktop.
- Microsoft Teams.
- Discord.

## **Idiomas**

#### Español:

Nativo.

#### Inglés:

Nivel medio.



1987 Febrero 1

### Perfil

Desarrollador web con habilidades para solucionar problemas y experiencia en creación de sistemas web. Capacitado para el trabajo en equipo bajo la metodología ágil SCRUM. Autodidacta y siempre dispuesto a aprender nuevas herramientas de desarrollo para mi crecimiento personal y profesional.

# Contacto



+34 663 48 34 44



chalds87@gmail.com



Galicia - España



chalds.github.io

# Habilidades Blandas

- Liderazgo.
- Pensamiento analítico.
- Trabajo en equipo.
- Perspectiva.
- Resolución de problemas.
- Paciencia y perseverancia.
- Enfoque y productividad.
- Proactivo.

# **Christian Lopez**

Desarrollador Web

### Datos académicos

Colegio Universitario Francisco de Miranda Ingeniero Informática | 2012 - 2016

Curso Online Platzi Curso de Programación Básica | 2017

Curso Online Platzi Introducción a PHP | 2017

# Referencia personal

**Daniel Gómez Matos** +34 722 63 76 00